Juned Khan

Agra, Uttar Pradesh, India



khanjunaid046@gmail.com



8445452656



linkedin.com/in/juned-khan

Summary

I have 3.5 years total experience in PHP Developer profile also 2.5 years of experience on Laravel Developer Position and 1 year of Core PHP and Codelgniter frameworks. Currently, I am learning React Js to become a full-stack developer. Along with my other skills MYSQL Database, JavaScript, Ajax AWS Cloud Computing Services, Web Hosting, Git.

Experience

Chetu Laravel Developer

Chetu. Inc.

Mar 2020 - Present (1 year 5 months +)

A Laravel Developer is responsible for creating and implementing an array of Web-based products using PHP, MySQL, Ajax, and JavaScript. I develop back-end components and Rest API service to connect the application with other web services, and assist front-end developers by ensuring their work integrates with the application and learned team management.

Laravel Developer

Homizone

Mar 2019 - Mar 2020 (1 year 1 month)

In this Organization, I implement Homizone project from scratch. Homizone Project-based on real state market and completely developed on Laravel Framework 6.0

I individually handle this project on the server-side and also database structuring.

I am integrating many APIs Like Payment Gateway, Paynimo E-natch (Auto debit) service, Image compression, social auth Login, Online Document Sign (Leagality.com), Online document verification (Adhaar API). I have implementing Some API to connect our IOT service.

PHP Web Developer

Wmts Private Limited

Aug 2018 - Feb 2019 (7 months)

In this organization, I have learned the Codelgniter framework and work some websites based on the Codelgniter framework and learned how to use Oops in Codelgniter and Learned MVC pattern and what is model, controllers, view etc. I have work some project based on Codelgniter Framework like Mission Bol, Hopeberrry Hospitality, etc.

PHP Web Developer

Graphics Central

Jan 2018 - Aug 2018 (8 months)

In this organization, I am starting my carrier it is the best memory of my life because my colleagues are very helpful and guide me on how to do work with live projects and how to write code with standards.

In this organization, we have complete some projects like GFB, Graphics Central, Manna Win Trade. Some live project url: https://gfb.com.au/, https://graphicscentral.com.au/, http://mannawintrade.com/

Education



RAJA BALWANT SINGH MANAGEMENT TECHNICAL CAMPUS, AGRA.

Diploma, Computer Science & Engineering

2014 - 2017

I have Completed Diploma in Computer Science & Engineering (2014-2017) from Raja Balwant Singh Polytechnic College Bichpuri, Agra under BTEUP with 73.79% aggregate.



N. C. Vedic Inter College

High School, Computer Science

Jul 2011 - Apr 2013

I have complete my Intermediate Board of Uttar Pradesh from N. C. Vedic Inter College, Sultan Pura Agra with 68% aggregate.



N. C. Vedic Inter College

High School, Computer Science

Jul 2010 - Apr 2011

I have complete my High School Board of Uttar Pradesh from N.C. Vedic Inter College, Sultan Pura Agra with 54% aggregate.

Licenses & Certifications



PHP developer - Croma Campus Pvt. Ltd.

CCN-22235257

Skills

Laravel • PHP • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap • CodeIgniter • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • MySQL • JavaScript • AJAX